A heartwarming tale of murder.
Brother's Keeper is a documentary film directed by Bruce Sinofsky.
This documentary by Joe Berlinger and Bruce Sinofsky
details the murder trial of Delbert Ward.
Delbert was a member of a family of four elderly brothers, working as semi-literate farmers and
living together in isolation from the rest of society until William's death.
Self, played by Connie Chung.
Self, played by John Teeple.
Self, played by Delbert Ward.
Self, played by Roscoe Ward.
Self, played by Lyman Ward.
Brother's Keeper is a 1992 documentary directed by
Joe Berlinger and Bruce Sinofsky.
The film is about an alleged 1990 murder in the village of Munnsville, New York.
The film is in the "Direct Cinema" style of the Maysles brothers,
who had formerly employed Berlinger and Sinofsky.